Members who did not make it into the blue sky group.
I'll name this one too.
This team will be called
This team will be called "Spider Team".
Of course, I'm very disappointed.
But to be honest, I expected it.
I have no choice but to accept it.
I'm also frustrated that I'm able to accept it.
I want to do my best here and not give up.
I'm frustrated, too.
But I also feel like there's nothing I can do better.
I'm grateful for the environment I've been given
I'm grateful for the environment I've been given there.
I have to give it my all.
I can't contribute to the company.
I think I have to do my best here first.
We had a meeting to think about the future of Kuma group.
We were gathered for a presentation.
We, the members of Kuma group
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
We've been talking a little bit about the direction we want to take, based on our discussion the other day.
I've been given time to share that with you.
We've talked about the vocalist's desire to dance more, and we've come up with a plan to promote her.
I think that's a good point, and I'd like to promote it.
I thought it would be good if we could make a music video for everyone.
I thought it would be better if everyone had a chance to make a music video.
So we decided to make a music video.
We are going to shoot a music video first.
I think you did a great job on the debut single
I think you guys did a great job on our debut single.
I hope that everyone will work together again
I hope that everyone will work together again.
I really hope that we'll be able to work together again.
When we were talking about the previous episode...
I don't even know if the music video
I don't know if we can do it or not.
so we are not sure if we can do it or not.
We were also talking about how we
We were talking about how we wanted to make a music video
so we were more interested in having our
I'm more than happy that there will be a dance
I'm happy to have a music video
music video together.
from the very beginning,
I am very happy that we made the music video together as Kumogumi. I am grateful for that.
I'm grateful for the opportunity, and I want to do my best.
We don't have much time before the NV shoot, but we have prepared costumes for our activities as the Kumogumi,
I hope that the 11 of us will work together as a united group in these costumes after the fitting.
After the announcement of the music video shooting, we will have a costume fitting for our activities as Kumogumi.
I'm going to change my hair style after consulting with the staff.
My third one is by Meeser, and this one is by YUHO, isn't it good?
What's that?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's in the freezer.
Oh, yeah?
Crab.
Leave it.
Oh, wow.
Or like this.
Oh, it's on.
I think I'll wear my hair like this.
How about this?
It'll be about 3 inches shorter.
It's going to be curled up a little bit, and it's going to float a little bit off the shoulder.
Almost there.
So that I can see your face.
Just here.
Take it down.
It could go either way.
Both of you change.
Just look at me and give me some eye contact.
Okay.
And so it was decided... Thank you... Bye... On this day, we gathered for a lesson on choreography for a music video. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
First of all, before the lesson, we listened to a song that was given to us.
I'd really like to share it with you all, but it's still a secret.
Yes, this is the song for everyone's spider step.
I was a little bit moved by it.
I hope that Spider Troupe can catch up with Bauzal Troupe
I hope to catch up with the Bauersal team in dance skills and other things.
to catch up with the Bauersal group in dance skills and so on.
The song also encouraged us.
I thought that I want to do my best with this song to make everyone smile
I want to do my best with this song so that I can bring smiles to everyone's faces.
Now the lesson is about to start.
Right, left, right, left.
But once I let my body memorize it, I think I will be better if I don't think about it, so it was really difficult.
I think it is probably the most difficult waka song I have ever played.
There were so many detailed choreographies.
There are a lot of complicated choreographies.
If I forget one of them
I can't get into it the next time.
That's the hard part.
It's so difficult.
I can't think straight.
I don't know what to do.
I'm in a hurry.
It's my least favorite part.
I mean performance in general... but dancing... and there are a lot of inexperienced members.
There are a lot of inexperienced dancers in Kumogumi.
I need to improve the quality of my performance.
I think it's difficult to get the same level of quality as the other members.
Of course we practice and work hard.
I will of course work hard in practice, but I also want each individual to study how to present themselves and how to use facial expressions.
and how to use facial expressions.
I want to be able to perform well.
The challenge for the Spider Team is to improve their performance ability.
Many members say that they are not good enough in terms of skills.
But I'm not good at dancing at all, so I'm trying to improve my skills.
The members are earnestly working to improve their skills.
In the midst of all this
I'm sitting in a chair watching the lesson.
Rian, who was bored with the lesson
In fact, she hurt her leg
so she decided to take it easy and observe the lesson.
Today, she changed her clothes and observed the lesson.
I feel bad for everyone at this important time of the year, but
But today is the day of the rehearsal.
I'm worried that I'll be left behind by the other students in the same group.
I'm also worried that I won't be able to participate in the practice properly.
I also feel sorry that I can't participate in practice properly.
But I have no choice but to practice.
I was able to practice what I can do today, even if it's only with my upper body.
I could practice what I could do today, even if it was only my upper body, so I could rest my knee and watch the movements several times or listen to the songs all the time.
Everyone can do that,
I hope I can do what I can do and improve before the MV.
Now, were you allowed to do that?
I have to move my legs.
Oh, I did.
Are you okay?
Don't be anxious.
Members following Rian-chan
Watching the lesson this time, we could see them following each other when they didn't understand something.
This is an idea that Hitomi Hasegawa mentioned at the last meeting.
I think it's easier for each person to express their opinions, so I think it's better to have fewer people in the group.
I think it's better to have fewer opinions than to have more opinions.
I think it's better to have a small number of people, so that each person can express their opinions easily.
And then we can improve on what we've noticed.
We all support each other to improve the performance of Kumogumi.
Now, Yuki-chan... oh, Yuki-chan is gone.
I guess this was the first lesson for the Spider group after they were separated from the Aozora group.
It was the first lesson for us.
Everyone was teaching each other.
They taught each other what they did wrong.
They told me I was making a mistake.
It was a great atmosphere.
It was a very friendly atmosphere.
Everyone worked together and taught each other
And we taught each other.
The music video is coming up in three days.
I hope we can show something good
I hope we can show you something good
We'll all practice hard.
I can't catch up with everyone.
And I'm not very good at going to the teacher to ask for help.
I'm not very good at going to the members to ask them to teach me when there are two of us working together.
When I was doing it alone
Today, Elegant Yamaguchi and Mana Mochinaga approached me and taught me in detail.
They taught me in detail, so I'm very grateful to them.
I'm also grateful to them.
I'm also grateful to the other members who told me what to do.
I thought that the unity of the Kumo group
I think it's a good thing that the dance teacher has done this so many times.
That's for sure.
We're going to get up and we're going to stay on our feet all the way to the end, and we're going to time it here.
And then at the end, we'll go right into it.
Let's go all the way up.
Let's go all the way up. Slowly.
Quickly, quickly.
Hitomi Nagasawa is good at dancing,
Hitomi Nagasawa and Mana Mochinaga, who are very good at dancing, are leading the quality of the dance.
There's something about this place.
This timing is even more frightening!
Is the timing of the three times good?
There's someone who's kind of long.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10 ... 58,59, ... The members of Kumugumi are building up their unity in this way for the shooting of the music video.
Let's do our best!
What kind of music video will it be?
Next time, I will shake hands for the first time. I will closely observe the first handshake of the Kumugumi members!
Wow, thank you very much. Wow, thank you very much. This handshake session, I will closely observe the first handshake of a homogumi member! Thank you!
I would be happy if you enjoyed talking with me or if you felt happy with my smile.
I'm really nervous, and I'm worried that my hands are going to shake.
I will do my best to make you feel really happy to shake hands with Misa-chan.
Misa Yaegashi narrated the music video.
I was really happy to hear that we could shoot the music video.
We all worked really hard on it and I can't wait for everyone to see it.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Bye bye!